ourtoolbar.com 2008-05-09

# Website Privacy

Website Privacy Policy

(Last Updated: February 22, 2007) 

Definitions

**“The Company”** means Conduit Ltd.  
**“The Website”** or **“the site”** means [www.conduit.com](http://www.conduit.com/) and/or other web domains owned and operated by the company and referring to the Conduit on-line platform or to other services provided by the company. 

Collection of Personally Identifiable Information  
We do not require site users or visitors to provide us with Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) In order to view the content in our Website or to browse the different sections of the Website. We may only collect PII from site users or visitors who choose to use the Conduit on-line platform to create and distribute a customized toolbar and by that become a licensed Conduit toolbar publisher. Any such collection of PII shall be performed in full accordance with the terms listed in this Conduit Website privacy statement. Conduit is the sole owner of the information collected on the Website. Any information we collect is collected for the primary purpose of enabling us to provide the Service to our users. We do not sell or rent PII to third parties. 

If your Personally Identifiable Information changes, you may correct or update it upon your login to our on-line platform by making the change on your personal information page. If you no longer desire our services or wish to delete or deactivate your account, you can contact us at . 

Registration

In order to create and maintain a customized community toolbar using the Conduit on-line platform provided in the Website, you must first complete a registration form within the Conduit toolbar creation Wizard. During this registration you are required to provide a user name, a password and a valid email address which are all necessary for identifying your toolbar and for validating your registration. We may use this information to contact you regarding the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. You have the option to provide us with additional information (such as company name, title etc.). We encourage you to submit additional information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site and offer you better support. 

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys or special promotional programs on our site. If you choose to participate, we will request certain PII from you. Participation in such contests or surveys or special promotional programs is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). We use this information to notify participants, to monitor site traffic, personalize the site or send participants email updates upon their approval. 

Choice/Opt-out  
You have the option to choose to receive occasional email updates from Conduit. Such updates can include a newsletter or other notifications in relation with the Conduit platform. We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your Personally Identifiable Information used for such purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you do not wish to receive any additional marketing materials from us, you can indicate your preference on our registration form. If you no longer wish to receive our email updates, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each update or by emailing us at: . 

“Tell-A-Friend”

Users of toolbars created using the Conduit environment may voluntarily choose to activate a “Tell-A-Friend” feature from within their toolbar. Upon such a use, the toolbar user will be referred to a designated page hosted on the Website allowing the user to send an email notification to his friend or to any other entity of his choice. If you choose to use our service to tell a friend about our site or toolbar, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Conduit uses this information for the sole purpose of sending and tracking the delivery of this one-time email. Conduit erases all third party email address provided using the “Tell-A-Friend” feature from its servers at least once a month. Your friend may contact us at to request that we remove this information from our database. 

Sharing Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties  
Conduit may use a third party service provider only for the purpose of distributing emails to its registered users and/or toolbar publishers. Conduit shall provide this service provider with relevant email addresses of its registered users and/or toolbar publishers and with the content of letters to be sent by the service provider. The service provider is prohibited from using these email addresses or the content of the letters for any other purpose. Conduit does not share any collected PII with any third party other than in the way mentioned in this clause. 

Conduit may use a third party service provider to mange and operate a discussion board within the Website domain. The use of the discussion board is subject to an initial approval of the discussion board Terms of Use. Users of the discussion board may choose to place PII on messages they post. If you use a the discussion board on this Website, you should be aware that any Personally Identifiable Information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these discussion boards, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the Personally Identifiable Information you choose to submit in these forums. 

Conduit may engage in business relations with third party companies and offer unique services to clients of such companies within a private label environment. For such purposes, some pages of the Website may be branded with both the Conduit brand and the third party brand. The third party cannot use the private label environment to collect any PII and is prohibited from doing so. The Conduit Website privacy statement shall apply to all of the pages in the private label environment. 

If you entered the Website by clicking an affiliated link or promotion on another Website, or if you used a site that provides universal registration services to sign up for Conduit services, we will store the ID of that affiliate site in our database along with your computer's User ID. We do this to ensure that the affiliate site receives proper credit for any subsequent toolbar you may build using our platform. 

Conduit reserves the right to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website. 

Use of Cookies and Server Logs  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We occasionally use cookies on this site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. We set a persistent cookie to store your toolbar name and/or user name so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If you reject cookies, you will still be able to use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site may be limited. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any Personally Identifiable Information you submit while on our site. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site. Such cookies may be used to analyze the Website traffic in our site and monitor operational performance of the Website. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Conduit only and does not cover the use of cookies by any other third party. 

Server logs capture certain non-Personally Identifying data, such as the time and date of a web visit, the browser and operating system being used, the IP address or domain name of the user's ISP, and the web URL a user linked from. This information is generally used to help us plan system enhancements when necessary and to provide content which is compatible with our visitors' web browsing systems. We do not use server logs in any way that may disclose your PII. 

Public Display of Personally Identifiable Information  
Conduit provides a platform for creating toolbars serving assorted communities. All toolbars are publicly available for download from the Website and may be used free of charge. For promotional purposes, Conduit may occasionally post testimonials or case studies in different sections of the Website. Such posts may include PII of registered users or toolbar publishers as provided and approved for this public use by these registered users or toolbar publishers. For purposes of promotion and community peers-review, Conduit may also display toolbars created by registered users or toolbar publishers in a gallery section within the Website. Such display shall only include the toolbar name and shall not include any other PII. 

Security  
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can contact us at . 

Changes to this Privacy Statement  
If we decide to change our Website privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

TRUSTe Privacy Program  
Conduit is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Website. Because this Website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact . If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at: <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

The TRUSTe program only covers information that is collected through this Website, and does not cover information that may be collected through any software downloaded from this Website. 

**Conduit  
71 Stevenson Street, Suite 400  
San Francisco, CA 94105**

Let us show you how easy and quick it is to create your Conduit community toolbar
